(Amy:)Bernadette is with
Priya and Leonard.
(Amy:)Message received.
(Amy:)Commence operation
"Priya Wouldn't Wanna Be-ya."
(Penny:)Hey. Seriously?
(Penny:)Didn't you get enough of this
cliquey crap in high school?
(Amy:)I wish. A clique
requires friends.
(Amy:)- I didn't have any.
- None?
(Amy:)I used to take my lunch
down to the maintenance room
(Amy:)and eat with the janitor.
It was nice until his wife
called me a puta
(Amy:)and made me stop.
(Amy:)Hang on.
(Amy:)It's the wildebeest.
(Amy:)Priya just made a snide comment
about your acting career.
W-What the hell did she say?
(Amy:)She thinks it's cool
you're following your dream,
(Amy:)no matter what.
(Penny:)That bitch!
(Amy:)How do you want
to handle it?
(Penny:)Um, okay.
(Penny:)Tell Bernadette to tell Priya
that I'm on my way to Prague
(Penny:)to shoot a movie
with Angelina Jolie.
(Leonard:)Got it.